# Tyler Bertmore

# **Software Engineer**

#### Contact

## **Objective**

# tylerbertmore@gmail.com

github.com/tylerbertmore linkedin.com/in/tylerbertmore

**Portfolio:** <u>tylerbertmore.com</u> (702) 779-5803

I'm a former teacher turned Software Engineer that specializes in Full Stack JavaScript and seeks to always learn new technologies to stay ahead of the tech world curve. I use my teaching experience to approach everything with a learner's mindset.

#### Education

# **General Assembly**Software Engineering Immersive

My time here taught me the ins and outs of being a Software Engineer.

#### **Key Skills**

Frontend	Backend
HTML	JavaScript
CSS	Python
JavaScript	SQL
	MongoDB

## Frameworks / Libraries

Frontend	Backend
React	Node
Bootstrap	Express
Materialize	Django
Semantic UI	Passport
jQuery	

## **Projects**

Help Desk - GitHub - View Live Version

An IT ticketing system with full CRUD and user roles.

Technologies Used: MongoDB, Express, Node, Bootstrap, JavaScript

#### Wayfarer - GitHub - View Live Version

Travel app that lets users post about destinations in popular cities. *Technologies Used*: Python, Django, PostgreSQL, Materialize

#### Walk With Me - GitHub - View Live Version

Dog walking app that lets users make appointments to walk dogs. **Technologies Used:** MongoDB, Express, Node, JavaScript, Passport

#### Yurblegatchi - GitHub - View Live Version

A fun clone of the 'Tamagotchi' craze from the 90's.

Technologies Used: HTML, CSS, JavaScript

#### **Experience**

General Assembly • Software Engineer - Remote

September 2020 – December 2020

AMES English • Teacher - Can Tho, Vietnam

June 2017 – September 2020

Planet Hollywood Casino • Valet - Las Vegas, NV

February 2014 – January 2017